Rebels with a claus.
The Naughty Nine is a family, adventure, comedy film directed by Alberto Belli.
Fifth-grader Andy finds himself without a present
from Santa on Christmas morning.
Realizing he must have landed on the “naughty list” and feeling unfairly maligned, Andy pulls together a team of eight other
naughty-listers to help him execute an elaborate heist on Santa’s Village at the North Pole to get the presents they feel they deserve.
Andy, played by Winslow Fegley.
Santa Claus, played by Danny Glover.
Dulce, played by Camila Rodríguez.
Lewis, played by Anthony John Joo.
Ha-Yoon, played by Imogen Cohen.
Rose, played by Clara Stack.
The Naughty Nine is an American Christmas heist
television film directed by Alberto Belli.
The film stars Winslow Fegley, Camila Rodriguez, Derek Theler, Deric McCabe, Clara Stack,
Anthony Joo, Ayden Elijah, Imogen Cohen, Madilyn Kellam, and Danny Glover.
It premiered on Disney Channel on November 22, 2023.
The film explores themes of santa claus, heist,
north pole, christmas, naughty kids.
The tone is lighthearted.